Did you call for me. honey?
No. Mom.
Huh. you're up early. kiddo.
What can I get you for
breakfast?
Chocolate chip pancakes.
You got it. love bug.
And for the tracks.
do you think I'll win.
No. you won't.
Because there's no finish
line. how can you win?
You just gotta make your own.
I win!
What's wrong?
I had another nightmare.
Kids. get dressed. We're
leaving in 20 minutes.
Grab your things.
Don't forget our baseball
stuff.
Please. don't kill me! Don't
hurt me!
Please!
Open the door!
Lucas. what are you
doing to her?
I hate you! I'm telling Mom
and Dad.
Mom. the camera.
Oh. here you go. hon.
Thanks.
Remember when we went camping
on our second date?
Hey. Dad.
Hey. Champ.
Hey. you guys wanna know what
bears
call people in sleeping bags?
What?
Soft tacos.
Stop it.
I don't get it.
He means the bears are gonna
eat us.
Lucas. leave your sister
alone.
Mom!
I wanted to hit some high
pops today. but it's raining.
Oh. sweetie. no. the rain's
gonna clear. okay. I promise.
Where's my hug.
I love you. Mom.
I love you too. sweetie.
Lucas. Lucas. Lucas.
Lucas. Lucas. Lucas!
Now batting. Lucas
Coyle! The crowd goes wild!
Hey!
Shut up.
Tessa. get the ball.
What are you. scared? Get the
ball.
No. you threw the ball. Go get
it.
Get the ball!
Stop being a jerk.
Tessa!
Hey. kids. time to eat!
We want food. we
want food. we want food!
Rich. how long till the
burgers?
Give me about five. hon.
Now. Jack. it's important to
marinate
the ketchup with the onions.
So. the secret ingredient.
is sharp cheddar cheese.
And you put it all on an
English muffin instead of a bun.
- Hey. honey?
- Yeah?
Looks like it might storm.
We might have to head back
tonight.
No. I think we'll be all
right.
Think so?
- Dad?
- What?
Look. someone's watching us.
Hey.
Hello.
What are you doing over there?
Who was that?
It was just someone lost.
Nothing to worry about.
Where's Tessa?
Where's Tessa? Tessa?
Tessa.
Hey. Tessa!
- Tessa.
- Tessa!
You guys stay here
in case she comes back.
Okay.
It's okay.
Out!
Oh. hi.
What's your name?
Out.
My name's Tessa.
I just need to get my ball.
Out!
It'll just take a minute.
Tessa!
You boys stay here. okay.
don't move!
Okay.
Help!
Tessa!
No!
I hate you!
I'm telling Mom and Dad!
Monsters are real!
You almost done. Jack?
Just about.
Huh. it's a shame you
never had a chance to work
those old film projection
platters.
They spin round and round.
and you had to know exactly
when to switch the next
platter from a little pop
in the corner of the screen in
between.
It was a beautiful bit of
business when you got it right.
Now you got buttons you push on
and off.
There's no human element
anymore.
Are you sure you haven't
reconsidered selling this place?
Na. it's done. This place
is a relic now anyway.
Asked me if I'm on drugs.
I said. it's none of your
business.
Then I.
Lucas!
Now batting. Lucas Coyle!
Hey. Mom. I got dinner.
Chicken that you like.
Fried?
Grilled.
Lucas.
I told you. I brought dinner.
Luke. where are you?
Lucas. Lucas. where are you?
What the hell are you doing?
You still haven't fixed that?
No. I will. all right?
It's been six months.
How have you not done
this? What else do you do?
I said I'll fix it.
Oh. I bought you dinner.
I'm not hungry.
I know. I saw the mess
you left on the counter.
You know what tomorrow is.
right?
Yes.
It means a lot to Mom.
And Zoey'll be there?
Your daughter.
So there are a lotta different
species
that have parasites.
You have humans. animals. plant
life.
you know. those sorta things.
Right. but why doesn't
it just kill the host?
Well. the relationship between
the two
is a version of symbiosis.
I mean. in some ways. both
need each other to stay alive.
It becomes mutualistic and
benign.
See. that's where I just get
confused.
That's okay.
Oh. we're gonna miss you. by
the way.
Aw. thank you. Riley.
Yeah.
I think he's got a crush on
you.
Oh. stop.
Give me that. Okay.
You're up early. kiddo.
What can I get you for
breakfast?
Chocolate chip pancakes.
You got it. love bug.
Amherst Bay. huh?
It's nothing too fancy.
Got a big backyard. That's
pretty cool.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll get a dog.
name her Rizzo.
You sure you don't wanna come?
I don't know.
You're not their babysitter.
Jack.
They're grownups.
One day. you're gonna have to
start living your own life.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I know you don't
like to talk about it.
No. it's okay.
I came here to congratulate you.
This is crazy you're
gonna be a vice principal.
I know.
I know. ah.
I got something for you.
Oh boy.
Oh my God.
Crazy. right?
Wow. I remember this.
Yeah.
You weren't going. and
my boyfriend dumped me
so he could take Debbie
Shellhorn.
And then you stepped up.
What is it?
Why are we just friends? Tell
me again.
Look. you don't have to come
tonight if you don't want to.
Is that why you brought me
coffee?
No. I just hate pulling
you into my family's drama.
You are not pulling me in.
And I'm not afraid of them
either.
Oh my God.
This is. wow. I can't
believe you kept this.
Had to.
I.
I decided Zoey can stay in
this room
till Tessa comes back.
Okay.
Hey. Uncle Jack.
Hey. Zoey. how's it going?
Good. where's Dad?
He wasn't feeling good. but
he'll be back at the house.
How was school?
Okay.
- Just okay?
- Mm-hm.
All right. Why don't you
give me a minute. okay?
I wanna talk to Mom.
So Lucas decided not to
show up again. huh? Typical.
Listen. I know we decided on
just this weekend originally.
but is there any way that. um?
There's this whole shit
show going on at work
with his girl. man. fucking
bitch.
Can you. um. look. I
don't know about Monday.
Shouldn't you be asking her
father?
Oh cut the shit. Jack. we
all know that you're the one
who makes the decisions around
here.
It's not like he responds to me
anyway.
Can you at least
pretend to be her mother?
Can't you see what you're
putting her through?
She wasn't my idea.
Look. I'll come get
her on Wednesday. okay?
Is that good?
She likes being with you.
And your mom would like to have
her.
Right. Zoey?
What?
Hey. any chance I could get
like 10 bucks for gas back?
I'm on empty. and I don't
get paid till next Friday.
Take it.
Thanks.
Okay. bye. You're
the best.
King Jack!
You all right?
Mm-hm.
Okay. Zoey. come on over here.
You can blow out the candle this
year.
Are you sure?
Yes. come on.
Okay.
I'm gonna sing a little
song. then you blow it out.
Okay.
♪ Happy birthday. Tessa.
happy birthday. Tessa ♪
♪ Happy birthday. Tessa ♪
Okay.
Yay!
Okay. I'm gonna cut the cake
now.
I know everybody wants a slice.
No no. where are you going.
Lucas?
Hey. no. no no.
Everybody has to stay
and have a piece of cake.
Ugh.
You know. I ask for one
thing every damn year.
Why can't I have that?
It's been 25 years. Mom.
We're still celebrating
Tessa's eighth birthday?
We don't even celebrate our own
birthdays.
We don't even celebrate
Zoey's. and she's still alive!
We celebrate Tessa's birthday
because she's not here.
And we owe here that!
We don't owe her anything!
Oh.
Tessa's cake.
You.
- You!
- Hey. Mom!
- Stop it!
Stop. Mom. Mom. stop it!
Tessa is dead!
Dad's dead. They're both fucking
dead.
No! You're wrong!
She's coming back. She just
disappeared.
She's still out there.
Not in front of Zoey. please.
If both of you had supported
me.
if both of you had listened to
if you'd both been better big
brothers
and taken care of your sister.
maybe she'd be here now
and not out there wondering
where her mother is!
We could never have a nice time
with you.
What do you want? What
do you want from me!
Do you want me to say I'm sorry.
again?
Maybe you both have lost
faith.
but I haven't.
She is out there.
And she's coming back.
Get out.
Just get outta here.
Get outta my house!
I want all your stuff
outta here by the morning!
Done.
Good!
No!
What?
Uh.
Are you okay?
I don't like it when you and
Grandma yell at each other.
I don't like it either.
Why does she keep saying
Aunt Tessa's coming back?
I don't understand.
Hey. good news.
You don't have to sleep
on the couch anymore.
Really?
It's Tessa's old room
actually.
I helped Grandma clean it out.
Do you want some?
Thank you. Princess.
This is for you.
That was Tessa's.
I think you should have it.
Thank you.
It's pretty.
I love you.
You know that. right?
I love you too. Dad.
Demonstration.
You are gonna be red. I'm gonna
be black.
So if I roll the die. I get a
two.
So. basically...
Your opponent across from you.
Mom?
You okay?
Yeah. it's just your brother.
He ruins everything.
How many years are we gonna do
this?
We've searched everywhere.
So have the police.
We've hired private
investigators.
We've spent money we don't have.
We've exhausted everything.
It's time we move on.
We all know what happened out
there. Mom.
And you're the only one
who hasn't accepted it.
You don't understand the
truth.
It was your fault!
No.
Now. it wants you.
Go away!
Lucas. please!
Open the door!
Lucas. what are you doing to
her!
I hate you! I'm telling Mom
and Dad!
It's okay. Lucas. come in.
Tessa. is that. is that you?
I'm so sorry.
I've been waiting for you.
Lucas.
Do you want to hit some
high pops?
It wasn't my fault!
Lucas.
Lucas!
Thank you so much for being
here today.
so that we may share in
the life of Lucas Coyle.
Whenever I'm called upon to
speak at a time like this.
I'm often directed to the words
of Moses.
specifically. Psalm 90.
Teach us to number our days
that we may gain a heart of
wisdom.
Teach us to number our days
so that we may gain a heart of
wisdom.
I'm so sorry
for your loss. Jack.
If there's anything you need.
let me know.
Are you thirsty?
You look like your father in
that suit.
I don't wanna do this.
All these people. looking
at me. judging me.
like what kinda mother would
let her son get to that point?
No one thinks that.
I wanna spread his ashes.
What's he doing here?
Just say hi. Mom.
I'm gonna go wait in the car.
We need to wait till
everyone leaves. Mom.
Jack.
Really happy you came.
Lucas meant the world to me.
I know.
Did you know that we've been
talking
the last couple months?
Really?
It was a big step for him to
reach out.
I thought he was finally getting
it.
Even came to a few meetings.
I didn't know that.
Listen. when you're ready to
talk.
you know where to find me.
I will. Thank you.
I love you. Jack.
Love you too.
Has the family had time to say
their final farewells?
Yeah. okay.
Zoey!
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Zoey. honey. are you...
There's something in there
with Daddy!
Uncle Jack. please don't!
It was nothing. Zoey. It's
okay.
We're here for you. sweetie.
Okay?
Here. come here. baby. sh.
Say hi to your mama.
How did he look?
You could have come in.
Don't do too well at these
things.
Sometimes you have to do
things you don't wanna do.
I know. I know.
Hey. baby.
Look. I'm sorry I'm late.
I had to stop somewhere because
I wanted to get you this.
Hey. Steff. let's bounce.
Let's go.
Give us a second.
So sorry about your brother.
man.
No. not you.
Jack. can you. um?
I'm obviously going through a
really rough time right now.
and can Zoey...
I need you to take her.
You're seriously leaving right
now?
I'm sorry.
Bye. sweetie pie.
Where are you going?
Stay with your Uncle
Jack for a smidge. okay.
You know how your mom gets.
Hey. let's go to Grandma.
okay?
I'm gonna take you to the car.
Okay.
All right. let's go.
Hey. you think you can
help me out a little?
Anybody leave any money
in those cards in there?
Yeah. they did. but it's for
Zoey.
I just wanted to have
a few friends over.
you know. for a little
thing to celebrate Luke.
Think you could chip in for it?
I'm done.
Okay.
Never mind.
How much you get?
Nothing.
Nothing?
Just leave me alone.
What are you doing?
I miss him.
I miss him too.
You know. when we were kids.
Tessa was afraid to put
her hands in the cement.
So your dad did it first.
He was brave. just like you.
Someone's here.
Mommy.
Do you ever hear voices?
What kind of voices?
I mean voices that aren't
really there.
Do you?
Could it be the thing
that's buried in the basement?
Who told you that?
I heard you and my
dad talk about it once.
What if he's trying to tell me
something?
Come here.
Hey.
Hey. Jack. Glad you came.
How you holding up?
To be honest. not good.
To be honest. that's natural.
You're not supposed to feel
good. Jack.
Place looks great.
Yeah. A Heritage Museum.
Honor the past. just don't live
in it.
What's on your mind. Jack?
What did you and Lucas talk
about
the last time you saw him?
He was using.
He wanted to get better for
Zoey.
He knew she needed him.
but his demons were still too
strong.
How's your mother?
The same.
They have her on four
different meds right now.
I know they're making her
physically sick.
and none of them seem to be
helping.
I hate your mother's doctors.
It helped at first.
You really think so?
I don't know.
Your mother is addicted to her
meds.
She's my sister.
I knew her before all this
happened.
and I've seen the wonderful
person inside.
I know.
She won't change.
But she can.
It happens. People do it all the
time.
But she chooses not to.
She replays that day over and
over again.
She just won't accept
that Tessa and your father are
gone.
And with Lucas gone. I'm
afraid she's gonna drift
deeper and deeper until
there's no reaching her.
Jack. don't fall into your own
loop.
That would be a real tragedy.
- Thanks.
- Yeah. whew.
So. how's Zoey doing?
She's gonna stay with us for a
while
until Steffi gets her shit
together.
I can't imagine what that
little girl is going through.
I wanna give her some sense of
normalcy.
something Lucas and I never had.
She just needs some guidance.
That's all any of us are looking
for.
We're gonna spread
Lucas' ashes tomorrow.
It would mean a lot to
me if you were there.
Then I will be there.
- Bye.
You all right?
Are you sure this is the right
place?
Absolutely.
Do you wanna say something?
Lucas. I just want you to
know that I love you. and uh.
I'm sorry.
Do you have the urn. sweetie?
Where is it? Where's the urn?
I don't know. You guys had it.
I thought you had it.
I didn't have it. I thought
you held onto it. sweetie.
All right. come on.
You lost it. Jack.
How could I have misplaced
this?
How could it just disappear?
Maybe somebody took it.
I don't know.
Mom. please. if you see it. let
me know.
I'm gonna go check in the car.
All right. I'll come with
you. We'll be back. okay?
Did Tessa really disappear out
here?
She did.
How do you know?
Well. we couldn't find her.
We just
lost her.
Do you really think
she's still out here?
I do.
Why didn't you continue
looking for her?
Zoey. do you wanna go
look for Tessa with me?
Where did they go?
Tessa!
- Tessa!
Tessa. where are you?
Tessa!
Grandma. are you okay?
My Grandma's hurt!
Can you help me?
I'm gonna get help. Please be
okay.
Mom!
Zoey!
She's not here.
Go back to the car.
There's a gun in the trunk.
under the spare tire.
Jack. you're scaring me.
This isn't gonna happen again.
Okay. all right.
Mom!
Zoey!
Zoey?
Is that you?
Mom? Mom. wake up.
Are you okay?
Where is Zoey?
Mom!
911. what's your emergency?
My mom has collapsed.
She's breathing but
otherwise unresponsive.
Zoey. where are you?
Where did you go?
Zoey? Zoey?
Who are you calling?
Do you think she's gonna be
okay?
What is this?
What are you doing here. Zoey?
Grandma fell to the ground.
This nice lady is calling for
help.
Hang up the phone.
Where did you get this?
You need. yours.
Zoey. let's go. Come on. let's
go.
You were there that day.
weren't you?
Stay away from me. and
stay away from my family!
What is that. Uncle Jack?
Go to the car.
Liz is at the car. Lock the
doors.
Okay. lock the doors. Go!
Liz. something's out there.
Zoey. get in the car.
Lock the door. Don't
open it until I get back!
What the hell was that?
Is Grandma gonna be okay?
She will. I promise. Don't
worry.
What attacked us. Uncle Jack?
I don't know. I...
Is it gonna come after us
again?
No. it won't.
I shot it.
So. it won't get us?
No.
It's gonna be okay. all right?
Okay.
Mr. Coyle?
How's she doing?
She's doing better. She was
dehydrated.
That's part of the reason
why she lost consciousness.
What's really going on?
When was the last time she saw
a doctor?
It was like two years ago.
She doesn't like going to the
doctor's.
Well that's unfortunate.
because her blood pressure's
really low. and there are some
vitals
of hers that are concerning me.
I don't wanna jump to any
conclusions.
and it's hard to tell.
but she should really
go see her primary doctor.
Okay.
We went out
to spread Lucas' ashes.
and my mom collapsed out in the
woods.
We almost lost her.
And what'd the doctor say?
It's what they didn't say.
What aren't you telling me.
Jack?
Something was out there.
What do you mean something?
I'm not sure.
I know this may sound weird.
It wasn't human.
I think people create
monsters. real or imagined.
But you know. I looked
in the mirror one day.
and I didn't like what I saw.
And I realized if I didn't get
sober.
it was gonna consume me.
How'd you get through it?
Okay. so.
there are these two bull moose.
and their territories overlap.
And they confronted each other
one day.
and they started banging
heads. their thick skulls.
boom. boom. over and over again.
And then one of them hooked the
other's
antlers and broke its neck.
But now. it has to drag
that carcass around
until it's exhausted and dies.
I don't get it.
People choose their burdens.
And a person must choose
to put that burden down
before they can be free.
You get it?
Yeah.
Good.
Zoey.
Don't be afraid. Zoey.
Open your eyes. sweetheart.
How's my little girl doing?
Mom?
I need your help. Zoey.
Would you be a dear and
tighten this for me?
Don't be afraid.
It's nothing.
I don't want to.
I need you to do it.
No!
Do it now!
Atta girl.
Zoey. what's wrong?
My mom was here. and then it
took her!
Who took her?
The monster from the woods.
Can you check on my mom
tomorrow?
I'm worried about her.
and I wanna make sure she's
okay.
Sure.
Can you sleep on the chair
and watch over me tonight?
Of course.
I won't let anything bad happen
to you.
I love you. Uncle Jack.
I love you too. Zoey.
What happened?
Steffi.
Is she okay?
She's dead.
I'm so sorry.
What am I gonna tell Zoey?
This isn't fair to her.
You have to be there for
her. whatever she needs.
She just lost her father.
I can't tell her right away.
I mean. things just aren't
making sense lately.
I just got Lucas' toxicology
report back.
I thought he mighta had
drugs in his system.
I didn't see anything on
here. except his medication.
I wanna know if I'm missing
something.
Please take a look.
Okay. um.
I don't. I don't see anything.
What is this right here?
Phage lytic enzymes.
I believe that he took his
life
because of something deeper.
No. there's something else.
This was in Lucas' room.
What am I looking at?
It's what I saw that
night. It's what attacked us.
And look. this is Lucas'
handwriting.
It's the word he wrote in the
mirror
before he took his life.
What if this thing is Nix?
Do you know what nix means in
German?
Nothing. It means nothing.
You were out there that night.
That was no animal. okay.
This isn't nothing.
Is this the rabbit hole
you really wanna go down?
Yes.
Because there's nothing here.
Hi. Uncle Jack.
Hey. Zo.
Did you check on my mom?
Yeah.
Is she okay?
You're gonna stay with us for
a while.
She doesn't wanna say goodbye?
You know how your mom is.
I know.
I'm okay. Uncle Jack.
I want my mom to feel better.
Besides. I like it here best
anyway.
Let's get you to bed. kiddo.
Hugs.
Mm-hm. good night. Grandma.
I love you.
I love you too.
Good night.
I'll see you up there.
Okay.
She finally did it. didn't
she?
Did you lock all
the doors and windows?
Yes. no one can get in.
Not the monster from the
woods?
No.
Not the monster in the closet?
Nope.
What about the one in the
cellar?
Not that one either.
Good.
I promise I won't let
any of them hurt you.
Promise?
Promise.
Now get some sleep.
Night. Zoey.
Good night.
Hello?
Hello!
What are you doing. Uncle
Jack?
I'm proving to you that there
isn't
anything buried in the basement.
Thought you already said there
wasn't.
I wanna make sure for you.
Mm.
Can I help?
Who does that belong to?
It's my dad's.
Jack! What are you doing to my
floor?
This is unacceptable!
I. I...
Okay. Mom.
Ugh.
So?
Open it.
It's all the stuff from my
childhood.
My dad musta put it here.
What's that?
It's a videotape.
What does it do?
It plays movies.
So it's a phone?
It plays videos like your
phone.
It's what we used when we were
your age.
So that's it.
There's nothing in here.
Sometimes our imaginations run
wild.
We could think of some
really great things.
or we can conjure up
some really bad things.
Sometimes. if you tell the
same story over and over again.
it takes on a life of its own.
Like the Nix?
Where did you hear that?
I saw it on the mirror that
day.
And I heard my dad talk about
it.
He told me it was going to
destroy us.
All of us.
What did you see?
It doesn't matter what I saw.
The important part is that we're
letting
our imagination get the best
of us and it's not healthy.
What if you're wrong?
I think I have proof.
I found one of my videotapes
buried in the basement.
All the videotapes I made when I
was a kid
are gone. except this one.
We put our hands in the
cement when I was seven.
I got my video camera when I was
10.
Let's find out what's on there.
We want food! We want
food!
Okay. okay. we hear you.
We want food!
Rich. how long till...
You marinate the ketchup with
the onions
and just keep stirring it
around. okay.
Guys. guys. wait up.
Tessa. smile!
Did you see that?
You were dead.
Jack. that's not funny.
I'm not joking. see!
Nothing's there.
I love you. Mom.
Is that Tessa? I hear
her voice.
No. Mom. Liz is here.
Hi. Mrs. Coyle.
Good night.
I don't know what to believe.
I don't know what's real.
I don't know what to do with
my mom or how to help Zoey.
I need to find the truth.
Stop. stop!
Why are you doing this to
yourself?
There are answers on this
tape and out in the woods.
Lucas knew what this thing
was! It took his life!
If something happens to you.
who's gonna watch after Zoey?
I have to go out there.
Careful. Please.
Hey. Jack. come and find me!
Hey. Champ. you guys wanna
know what...
What?
Stay where you are.
Don't come back. They're all
dead.
The secret ingredient
is sharp cheddar cheese.
And then you put it on an
English muffin...
- Dad.
Someone's watching us.
Hello?
What are you doing over there?
Mister. are you lost?
Yeah. sorry.
Can you point me in the
direction of the main road?
Yeah. sure. It's right over
there.
You guys camping?
Yeah.
Just grilling up some burgers
right now.
Sharp cheddar cheese is
the secret ingredient.
And you put it all on an
English muffin instead of a bun.
You're a good man.
I see you have a nice family.
You should enjoy your time with
them.
They're actually pretty rowdy.
But I love them.
How about you? Got any kids?
No.
Well. uh. one. sort of.
Hm.
Well. you take good care of her.
I better get back.
Safe travels. Champ.
Bye. Dad.
Love you.
Who was that?
Just someone who was lost.
Nothing to worry about.
Dad!
Tessa is going into the pond!
Help her!
- Save her. Dad. help her!
- Dad. save her!
Tessa!
No.
I saw it.
I saw all of it.
Did you find what you were
looking for?
But did you talk to the old
woman first?
Then it's not inside you yet.
You need to go talk to her.
Would you like some hot cocoa
und some marshmallows?
Why am I here?
Who are you?
I explain.
My life
pain.
come from Fatherland. old
country.
Brought Nix here to drown.
Keep it from ones I love.
But it found you.
Your family.
Your pain now.
You're not real.
You don't see.
Only darkness.
In order to see. you first
have to open your eyes.
Hey. Jack.
Lucas?
I wanna show you something.
Come on. Tessa and I are
gonna hit some high pops.
It's okay. Jack. Come in.
Save Zoey.
Who are you?
You've taken everything from us!
I don't understand.
What else do you want?
Tessa. are you awake?
Hm.
Oh.
We're gonna go camping tomorrow.
Have fun just like the old days.
Oh.
I love you so much. my little
princess.
Tessa!
Richard!
Why didn't you help her?
I couldn't find her. honey!
She's not there!
Richard.
I'm sorry. I tried to save
her.
You didn't try hard enough.
I looked and I looked and I...
Shut up. Richard!
This is your fault. She's
dead because of you.
You were supposed to be watching
her!
Get off of him! You're gonna
kill him!
What the fuck are you doing?
Stop!
Donna?
Donna. are you home?
Oh for God sake.
Donna. come on!
How'd you get in here?
You left the front door wide
open.
You can't be doing stuff like
that.
I'm so sorry.
I'll never do that again.
Jack came to see me.
Well that's unfortunate.
He's worried about you. Donna.
Everybody's worried about
me. and it's pretty annoying.
Just leave me alone.
We're trying to help you.
You've gotta get off the meds.
All those pills. you
know that's not healthy.
What should I be on. Doctor?
Oh. oh. wait. I forgot.
I'm supposed to be positive.
aren't I?
Because everything's just peachy
keen.
You know. I loved
Lucas like he was my own.
Well he wasn't.
You
don't have a clue
about what it's like to lose a
child.
I do know. Donna.
Because I buried Lucas too.
Ha!
But who do I bury next?
You or Jack. or maybe Zoey?
Oh.
Just. get outta my house.
Now!
Mom?
♪ We go round ♪
Now my little princess.
would you like to dance?
How about you?
♪ Far above the ground ♪
♪ No sign of you around ♪
What the fuck is this?
Don't be so dramatic.
Be polite. Say hello to your
sister.
It left me in the woods.
You'll feel different when it's
in you.
It doesn't want you.
Maybe you're dying like me.
No more lies. No more tricks.
I saw what you did to Dad.
Say what happened out there.
I'm sick. Jack.
I've been sick for a very long
time.
That's the one good purpose it
served.
It kept me alive.
Where is it going?
You and Lucas weren't enough.
There's only one left.
And she's upstairs.
No! You stay with me. Jack!
You stay with me!
Mother needs you.
Get away from her! What are
you doing?
Where is she?
What'd you do with her?
She's not here.
I know she's here. She's
hiding.
Come on out. Tessa.
Don't be afraid.
Jack. I missed you!
I love you. Jack.
Ah!
Oh. ah. ah!
Mom?
You can't have her.
Neither can the Nix.
This thing has been inside of
you.
feeding off of you.
It needs you just as much as you
need it.
Open your eyes. Mom!
Open them!
I...
I didn't want to hurt you or
Lucas.
I'm sorry. Jack.
I...
Oh.
I wish...
I could have been a better
mother for you.
I needed you.
I needed a mother.
Stop staring at me!
Stop judging me! Stop
treating me like a monster!
Get away from me! You're not my
son.
You're nothing!
Oh.
I...
Take me to the pond.
It's where I belong.
It's where it belongs.
I don't think it's gonna
stay in me for very long.
And if it escapes. it's just
going to find someone else.
You need help.
It's too late for me.
But it's not too late for you
and Zoey.
Mom.
Please. I have to be
with Tessa one last time.
I know Tessa died there.
I know that now.
But I'm still here. Mom.
Which is why this is our only
choice.
Please.
I could never be the mother
you wanted.
But you were always the son I
needed.
I love you.
I'm ready.
Oh. you look beautiful.
my little princess.
I love you. Mom.
Aw. I love you too. my Tessa.
Well those are two easy.
How about that one?
Elk.
Okay. okay. Okay.
- Okay that one. behind you.
- I'm ready.
Uh. deer.
It's a cari-boo!
You got it wrong. You
did not pass the test.
I did.
I did. I got it wrong.
I'm gonna go talk to your
uncle for a second. You okay?
Yeah.
All right.
I wanna thank you for
everything.
I appreciate you taking
care of Zoey last night.
Of course.
She needed to be out of that
house.
I'm sorry. for everything
I've put you through.
I'm just...
I'm just glad you're okay.
I haven't been acting
like myself lately.
So. did you find what
you were looking for?
Honestly...
Come here.
Come on.
Hey.
Uncle Jack. you're here!
I missed you.
Are you hungry? You can have my
pancakes.
Thank you. Zoey.
Wow. so. I guess this is
goodbye.
I guess so.
Why can't we just go with Liz?
Sweetie. you guys can come and
visit me
anytime that you want.
I have something to tell you.
What?
I lied.
About what?
I wasn't ready to say goodbye
to my dad.
It's okay. Zoey.
You're not mad?
No.
When you're ready to say
goodbye. you'll know.
Yeah.
Why don't we go with Liz to
her place?
Stay there for a while. see how
it goes?
Really?
Really.
I would love that.
Would you like that?
Guess what?
What?
Liz thought that that animal
right there
was a deer. but it is a caribou.
A caribou?
A caribou.
Obviously.
It was obvious. I was wrong.
What am I gonna do?
You want some coffee or
something? Wanna check it out?
Can I get ice cream?
You know. I think
that we can manage that.
♪ Nothing. nothing ♪
♪ Nowhere you can hide ♪
♪ Cold and dark inside ♪
♪ Nothing. nothing ♪
♪ Nothing left to try ♪
♪ You can't even cry ♪
♪ In the place where it dwells.
the many voices will tell ♪
♪ A lie that keeps you unwell ♪
♪ Your own personal hell ♪
♪ Put you in your place ♪
♪ Where it won't let you face ♪
♪ The way out to the light ♪
♪ Of a perpetual night ♪
♪ Nothing. nothing ♪
♪ Like your hands are tied ♪
♪ Took you for a ride ♪
♪ Nothing. nothing ♪
♪ Will the fates decide ♪
♪ Your inside will die ♪
♪ Like a dog on a chain ♪
♪ It takes a toll on the brain ♪
♪ It only adds to the strain ♪
♪ And only nothing remains ♪
♪ Like a parasite metastasize ♪
♪ It will take away your hope
and it will suck you dry ♪
♪ Nothing. nothing ♪
♪ Nowhere you can hide ♪
♪ Cold and dark inside ♪
♪ Nothing. nothing ♪
♪ You can't even cry ♪
♪ It won't tell you the truth ♪
♪ It will tell it to you ♪
♪ It will never be true ♪
♪ Nothing. nothing ♪
♪ Everything is nothing ♪
♪ All around is nothing ♪
♪ Nothing. nothing ♪
♪ What you feel is nothing ♪
♪ It's never going away ♪
♪ No matter how much you pray ♪
♪ Nothing's here to stay ♪